http://www.deandeluca.com/privacy-policy-1

About Us
PRIVACY POLICYUpdated January 1, 2018DEAN & DELUCA is committed to protecting the privacy of certain data that is collected from you and that you submit when you access this web site or web sites under our operation and control (collectively, the “Site”). We recognize the sensitive nature of much of the information with which we are entrusted on a daily basis, and we are committed to high standards of privacy. We respect your privacy and providing you proper protection and management of any Personally Identifiable Information you choose to share with us. Personally Identifiable Information consists of any information by which you can be personally identified or contacted, such as your first and last name, home or other physical address (including street name and name of a city or town), telephone number or e-mail address.The following outline is intended to familiarize you with our policies for the gathering, use, maintenance and protection of private information. The examples given are intended to be for illustrative purposes only, and therefore, should not be considered a complete representation of our practices. Your privacy is important to us. DEAN & DELUCA will not sell, share, or rent your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Please review this policy carefully. DEAN & DELUCA reserves the right to change its privacy policy at any time, in which event the Site will contain a notice of the change. Changes will be effective immediately upon posting to the Site. By accessing the Site, you are indicating your agreement to DEAN & DELUCA’s privacy policy. If you have any questions or concerns about any of our practices, please contact us at customercare@deandeluca.com.COLLECTING YOUR INFORMATIONDEAN & DELUCA collects information from you at several different points on the Site in order to carry out business functions, provide the highest quality of service to you, facilitate the delivery of services or the fulfillment of an order. Most of the information we collect comes directly from you. DEAN & DELUCA may compile statistical information concerning the usage of the Site. This information allows DEAN & DELUCA to monitor its utilization and continuously improve its quality. Examples of this information would include, but not be limited to, the number of visitors to the Site, or to sections or pages within the Site, patterns of traffic flowing through the Site, length of time spent on the Site, or in sections or pages of the Site, the other sites that refer visitors to the Site, the pages of the Site that visitors frequently use as entry and exit points, utilization of the browser and operating systems and versions used by visitors to the Site, etc.In order to compile this information, DEAN & DELUCA may collect and store your IP address, your operating system version, your browser version, the pages you visit within the Site, the length of time you spend on pages within the Site, the site from which you linked to ours, search terms you used in search engines which resulted in you linking to the Site, etc. While all of this information can be associated with the IP address your computer had while you visited the Site, it will not be associated with you as an individual, or associated with any other information you may submit through the Site, or that DEAN & DELUCA may store about you for any other purposes.There will be times, such as when placing an order, subscribing to a service, registering on the site, registering to receive catalogs, participating in promotions, surveys and contests, at which we may request personal information such as your name, billing/shipping address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card information, etc. It is solely your choice whether or not you provide this information. However, should you choose not to provide the information, we may be unable to process an order, fulfill a service, or display certain content on our Web site.The Site is not directed to children. DEAN & DELUCA does not knowingly collect any personal information from children. If you are concerned about your child’s use of the Site, you may use web-filtering technology to supervise or limit access to the Site.DEAN & DELUCA has arranged with PowerReviews, Inc. (d/b/a Buzzillions) ("PowerReviews") to facilitate the collection of customer product reviews on products sold by DEAN & DELUCA. When you submit a product review to DEAN & DELUCA, you are also subject to PowerReviews terms of use and privacy policies (see http://www.buzzillions.com/public/legal/index_en_US.html). Accordingly, you should review those policies prior to submitting a review. Also, reviews you submit may be posted on both www.Buzzillions.com and our site.We may use third-party service providers to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over, but not your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of interest to you. This information is collected through the use of pixel tags or cookies. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can visit http:/www.networkadvertising.org/.USING YOUR INFORMATIONIn the course of our normal business activities, we may disclose collected information to both affiliates and non-affiliated entities, as we deem necessary and as described in this Privacy Statement. Additionally, we use the Personally Identifiable Information you provide for internal business purposes such as: analyzing trends and statisticsmember services including Web page personalization orderhistory and statusone-click ordering order confirmation and trackingsubscription servicesinforming you of new products, services, offers and information about DEAN & DELUCA.We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.We may use outside purveyors to ship orders directly, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. In connection with these services, it is necessary to share certain Personally Identifiable Information with such providers. We have informed these companies that they are not to retain, share, store or use Personally Identifiable Information for any secondary purposes.We may also share personally identifiable information with unaffiliated third parties if (1) you request or authorize it, (2) the information is provided to help complete a transaction for you as described above, (3) the information is provided to comply with the law, applicable regulations, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our terms of use or other agreements, or to protect our rights, property or safety, or the rights, property or safety of our users or others, (4) the disclosure is done as part of a purchase, transfer or sale of the company or any of its services or assets (e.g., in the event that we sell assets to another party, customer information may be one of the transferred assets), or (5) the information is provided to such third parties as otherwise described in this privacy policy. We endeavor to choose non-affiliates with similar standards to ours regarding the protection of private information. At times, we partner with third parties to provide specific services, such as the mailing of our newsletters. When you sign up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. We have informed these parties that they are not allowed to use Personally Identifiable Information except for the purpose of providing these services.We occasionally make our list of customer names and street addresses available to carefully screened companies and organizations whose product and activities might be of interest to you. To be removed from the list of persons whose information is shared with third parties, please send an e-mail to customercare@deandeluca.com or call 800.221.7714. You may also write to:DEAN & DELUCAAttn: Customer Care4727 S Emporia St Suite 133Wichita, Kansas 67216We also may share your Personally Identifiable Information and non-personal information, including your name, address, email address and any transactions you conduct on our website or offline with us with a third party advertising partner and its service providers in order to deliver tailored advertising to you that match your interests when you visit our website as well as other websites. Our advertising partner will make the data that we provide anonymous so that no one else will receive your Personally Identifiable Information.UPDATING YOUR INFORMATIONAt any time you may review, update, correct, or change the Personally Identifiable Information you have provided to us. You may also choose to no longer receive any communication from DEAN & DELUCA, however you may continue to receive communications from those companies we shared your information with prior to your notification to us. You may use our Web site, through the My Account pages, to change your information. Alternatively, you can e-mail us at customercare@deandeluca.com, or call us 800.221.7714.You may also write to us at:DEAN & DELUCAAttn: Customer Care4727 S Emporia St Suite 133Wichita, Kansas 67216DO NOT TRACK“Do Not Track” is a privacy preference that you can set in your Internet search browser that sends a signal to a website that you do not want the website operator to track certain browsing information about you. However, because our Site is not configured to detect Do Not Track signals from a user’s computer, we are unable to respond to Do Not Track requests. WEB COOKIESA cookie is a piece of data stored on the user`s hard drive containing information about the user. DEAN & DELUCA may use web site “cookies” in the process of compiling the statistical information mentioned above and to tailor certain pages of the Site for your browsing convenience. Additionally, we use cookies to identify one user from another and to track marketing promotions and apply promotional discounts. The cookies contain no Personally Identifiable Information. As our shopping cart functionality requires the use of cookies to function, you will not be able to make purchases on our site if you have disabled cookies in your browser. Once you close your browser, the cookie expires. You have the option of setting your browser to reject cookies, but our Site may not function correctly if you do. Refer to the Help feature of your browser for information on disabling cookies. LINKSThis Web site contains links to other sites (“Linked Sites”). The Linked Sites are not under the control of DEAN & DELUCA and DEAN & DELUCA is not responsible for the contents of any Linked Site, including without limitation any link contained in a Linked Site, or any changes or updates to a Linked Site. As such, DEAN & DELUCA is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. Further, DEAN & DELUCA is not responsible for webcasting or any other form of transmission received from any Linked Site. DEAN & DELUCA is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by DEAN & DELUCA of the site or any association with its operators. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects Personally Identifiable Information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.MEMBER SERVICESIn order to set up an account with DEAN & DELUCA, you must first complete the registration form. During registration, you are required to give your contact information (such as name and e-mail address). This information may be used to contact you about the services on our site for which you have expressed interest, such as Web page personalization, order history and status.CATALOG MAILING LISTIf you wish to subscribe to our catalog mailing list, we ask for contact information such as name and street address. We occasionally make our list of customer names and street addresses available to carefully screened companies and organizations whose product and activities might be of interest to you.To be removed from the list of persons whose information is shared with third parties, please send an e-mail to optout@deandeluca.com or call 800.221.7714. You may also write to:DEAN & DELUCAAttn: Customer Care4727 S Emporia St Suite 133Wichita, Kansas 67216You may continue to receive communications from those companies we shared your information with prior to your notification to us. Please note that because some mailings are prepared far in advance, allow up to 90 days for your request to be effective. We also honor all opt-out requests from DMAChoice.org.EMAIL LISTIf you wish to receive e-mail notifications from us about products, services and promotions, we ask for contact information such as name and e-mail address. To be removed from our e-mail list, please click “Unsubscribe” in your email message or send an e-mail to optout@deandeluca.com or call 800.221.7714. You may also write to:DEAN & DELUCAAttn: Email Opt-Out4727 S Emporia St Suite 133Wichita, Kansas 67216From time-to-time our site requests information from you via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.We send all new members a welcoming e-mail to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special offers, and a newsletter. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option to not receive these types of communications in every e-mail. You may also email customercare@deandeluca.com or call 800.221.7714 at any time.SECURITY/SAFEGUARDING INFORMATIONDEAN & DELUCA and the Site take precautions and steps to safeguard and protect the personal information obtained through the Site. However, no system for safeguarding personal or other information is 100% secure. For example, when our registration/order form asks you to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the customary encryption software used in the ecommerce industry - SSL. Additionally, our employees are trained to understand the importance of confidentiality and are required to adhere to our privacy policies and procedures. Employees who violate these policies and procedures are subject to disciplinary action. We employ numerous practices to protect against the disclosure of information for purposes unrelated to the performance of our business functions or to individuals other than those who must use it in the course of their work activities. These practices include the use of password protection of computer files, e-mail and voice-mail, and other physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards.GOVERNING LAW/LEGAL NOTICESThese terms and conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of New York, excluding its conflict of law rules. For additional information concerning legal claims associated with this Privacy Statement and/or your use of the Site, please see our Terms of Use. For information on our GDPR Privacy Policy, see here.
